Guide to the School of Hotel Administration Career Planning and Placement Office records, 1983-1990.
School of Hotel Administration Career Planning and Placement Office records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Hotel Administration Career Planning and Placement Office records, 1983-1990.
28-6-4078
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration. Career Planning and Placement Office.
1.4 cubic feet.
Printed materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes annual reports, surveys, studies of post graduate activities, Society of Hotelmen job bulletins and undergraduate and graduate resumes.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes annual reports, surveys, studies of post graduate activities, Society of Hotelmen job bulletins and undergraduate and graduate resumes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell Society of Hotelmen; Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration -- Societies, etc.
Subjects:
Hospitality industry -- Employees.; Hotel management.; Hotel management schools -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- 1983-1988, Annual Reports (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1984-1987, Curriculum (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1984-1985, Curriculum Review Process (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Class of 1984, Studies of Post Graduate Activities (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Class of 1985, Studies of Post Graduate Activities (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Class of 1986, Studies of Post Graduate Activities (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Class of 1987, Studies of Post Graduate Activities (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1983-1990, Professional Resume Books- Undergraduate and Graduate Students (Box 1)
- July 1969-June 1970, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 8)
- July 1970-June 1971, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 9)
- July 1971-June 1972, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 10)
- July 1972-June 1973, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 11)
- July 1973-January 1974, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 12)
- July 1975-June 1976, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 13)
- July 1976-June 1977, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 14)
- July 1977-June 1978, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 15)
- July 1978-June 1979, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 1, Folder 16)
- July 1979-June 1980, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 1)
- January 1983-June 1983, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 2)
- July 1983-June 1984, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 3)
- July 1984-September 1984, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 4)
- January 1985-December 1985, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 5)
- January 1986-December 1986, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 6)
- January 1987-December 1987, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 7)
- January 1988-December 1988, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 8)
- January 1989-December 1989, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Job Bulletins (Box 2, Folder 9)
- May 1084, "Analysis of the Survey Databases of the Curriculum Review Task Force" (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 1980s, Curriculum Review Surveys (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 1988-1989, Hospitality News (Box 2, Folder 12)